D/J Daryl Jacura

Full Stack Developer

- 07786986064
- d.jacura@sky.com
- Reading, Berkshire, UK
- Linkedin.com/in/daryl-jacura
- d.jacura@sky.com
- % Website

ABOUT ME

I am a skilled Full Stack web Developer with a wealth of knowledge from my course at Code Institute. I Use HTML, CSS, JavaScript, python, Flask, Django and a load of other different languages and programs to create a unique user experience.

I work quickly and effectively in getting things built. I am an excellent communicator who thrives in bright and enthusiastic teams.

SKILLS

9/10

HTML / CSS

7 / 10

JavaScript / jQuery

7 / 10

Django / Python

8/10

MongoDB

7 / 10

SQL / NoSQL

EDUCATION

GCSE

Little Heath secondary school 07/00 – 07/05

A-levels

Little Heath Secondary school 07/05 – 07/07

Full stack web developer

Code Institute

03/20 - 03/21

EXPERIENCE

Retail worker

Asda Tilehurst, 07/2005 – 05/2007

Shopfloor worker, working in the fresh produce section and bakery areas of the business.

- Working on the shopfloor stacking shelves and rotating stock
- Working as a cashier when needed
- Working in the warehouse sorting stock

Retail worker

McDonalds, reading gate, 05/2007 – 07/2007

Working on front of house and on the drive through area of the business and well as maintaining stock.

- Working on the drive through taking orders
- Working out front taking orders

Audi Accredited Master Technician

Reading Audi, 07/2007 - present

Started as an apprentice technician and worked my way up through the levels to become an IMI accredited master technician.

- Servicing and maintenance of light vehicles
- Diagnosing and rectifying vehicle faults
- Covering workshop control and mentoring staff
- Carrying out calibration on tools and equipment